Guide to the Harry H. Love papers, 1907-1964.
Love, Harry H. papers, 1907-1964.
- Sze, Julia 1940-1942 + N. D. (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Miscellaneous Notes on the Drought in China 1934 +N. D. (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Inbreeding, Miscellaneous Data, Odd Lectures, Etc. 1926-1934. (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Inbreeding, Miscellaneous Data, Odd Lectures, Etc. N. D. (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Inbreeding, Miscellaneous Data, Odd Lectures, Etc. N. D. (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Two Miscellaneous Reports, 1963 and N. D. (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Maps, Prints, etc. 1933-1934. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Publicity 1931-1934 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Winter Institute 1932-1934. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Letters of Appreciation 1925-1935 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Food Relief Feb. 25, 1932 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Chien, T. H. 1931-1934 and K. D. Budgets and related correspondence. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Chien, T. H. N. D. Budgets. '' (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Contracts and Arrangements 1930-1931. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Contracts and Arrangements 1932-1934 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Nanking - Correspondence, re: Dr. Love's coming to China 1930. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Nanking - Correspondence, re: Dr. Love's coming to China 1931-1934. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Hanking - Departmental Conferences 1927-1934. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Programs 1932-1933 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Nanking - Plans for Survey N. D. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Programs 1929-1933 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Nanking - Projects, Methods, etc. 1925-1933 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Nanking-Projects, Methods, etc. N. D. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Nanking - Reports 1926-1927. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Nanking - Reports 1933. (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Nanking - Projects, Methods, etc. 1925-1937, N. D. (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Nanking - Projects, Methods, etc. N. D. (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Reports 1932, N. D. (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Reports N. D. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Nanking - Rotary 1934-1935. (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Nanking - Tsing H U A Fellowship Examination 1933 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Hsuchow 1934 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Kiangsi - Report 1933. (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Shantung N. D. (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Yenching 1933-1931. Reports on regional wheat tests. (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Cotton - Competition, N. D. (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Cotton - Correlation tables 1932-1933. (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Cotton - Cross Breeding 1932-1933 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Cotton - Missing plots, length of Lint N. D. (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Cotton - Plot Technic Study 1930-1932. (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Cotton - Questionnaire 1927-1932 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Cotton - Seedlists N. D. (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Cotton Variety Test Hsuchow F. V. 1933. (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Cosmopolitan Club - Mr. Kerr 1934-1943. (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Cosmopolitan Club - Mr. Kerr 1944-1949 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Rotary International Jan. - Oct. 1938. (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Rotary International Nov. 1938-1949 and N. D. (Box 3, Folder 41)
- International Service Commission Report N. D. (Box 3, Folder 42)
- International Service Commission Report N. D. Exhibits A-F. (Box 3, Folder 43)
- International Service Commission Report Exhibit G, "Survey of Ithaca New York in International Understanding," N. D. (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets 1921-1940. (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets 1911-1944. (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets 1945-1946. (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Book written in Chinese N. D. (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Book written in Chinese N. D. (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Book written in Chinese N. D. (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets N. D. (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Rotary International - Surveys, etc., 1934-1943 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Rotary International - Surveys, etc., n. d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Rotary International - Surveys, etc., n. d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rotary International, 1935; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rotary International, Jan. - Sept. 1936 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Rotary International, Oct. 1936 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Rotary International, Nov. - Dec. 1936; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Rotary International, Jan. - June 1937 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Rotary International, June 1937-1938; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Immigration, 1934-1935; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Agricultural Missions Foundation files
  Agricultural Missions Foundation (or Incorporated) was located at 156 5th Avenue, New York City. Files contain bulletins and newsletters, minutes, reports, and scattered correspondence, 1938-1950.
  NOTE: Acc. #21/2/87 (Dean of NYS College of Agriculture Carl E. Ladd) also contains files on the Agricultural Missions Fdn.: Box 5, Folder 11, 1933-1934; Box 12, F. 2, 1936-1937 (Reisner); Box 14, F. 29, 1937-1938; Box 23, F. 50, 1942-1943. Acc. #23/2/749 (NYS College of Home Economics Records) on same: Box 12, F. 20-22, ca. 1930-1945 (Reisner, Merrill Palmer; rosters; curriculum).
  - Agricultural Missions Foundation, 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Agricultural Missions Foundation, 1945-1947; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Agricultural Missions, Inc., 1944-1946 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Agricultural Missions, Inc., Jan. - June 1948 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Agricultural Missions, Inc., July 1945-1950; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Mission, 1938-1942 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Includes student rosters, curriculum information, etc. on the school for missionaries sponsored by the NYS College of Agriculture, 1941 and 1942. Of special interest is a mimeo copy (14 pp. typescript single-space) of a letter, Apr. 11, 1940, from E. A. White, describing a journey he and colleagues made by train, bus, and mule from Rangoon into the mountains of North Burma; contains much comment on travel conditions, missionary activities, the standard of living and customs of the natives, orchids observed on the trail, etc. (Edward Albert White, 1872-1943, of the C. U. Department of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture, 1913-1939, and author of American Orchid Culture, 1942.)
  - Agricultural Mission, 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Includes a mimeo copy (2 pp. ts.) of a letter to Professor Charles A. Taylor and the Faculty of the School for Missionaries from an alumna, Nina M. Stallings, Chengtu, Szechwan Province, China, Jan. 12, 1943, concerning her work: "All that you have ever heard about this wonderful province is true and improving every season. There is the most unbelievable production in these fields." Mentions that she was in need of goat's milk, but did not know how to milk one; urges that the unit on goat husbandry include learning how.
- Foreign Student, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Foreign Student Committee - Miscellaneous, 1935-1946 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Student Correspondence, Sept. 1935-Oct. 1937 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Student Correspondence, Nov. 1937-Jan. 1938 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Student Correspondence, Feb. 1938-1945; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Foreign Student Committee, Mar.-Aug. 1935 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Foreign Student Committee, Sept.-Oct. 1935 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Foreign Student Committee, Nov. - Dec. 1935 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Foreign Student Committee, Jan. - June 1936 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Foreign Student Committee, July 1936-1938; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Foreign Student Lists, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Foreign Student Committee - Students, May 1935-July 1936 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Foreign Student Committee - Students, Aug. 1936-1937; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Opportunities for Pland Breeding in China, n. d. (Box 4, Folder 31)
- China Correspondence
  - Bates, Searle Nanking, China, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Bowen, A. J. - China, 1926-1929 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Buck, J. L. - China, 1926-1930 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Chen, C. C. - China (see also grad student folder), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - China Emergency Fund, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Clemons, Harry - China, 1926-1928 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Griffing, J. B, and Burgoyne, brothers on U. of N. faculty (Looting of Nanking), 9 pp. ts. cc., 1927, Mar. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Heh, C. M. - China, 1926-1930 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Kuo, T. S. - Nanking, China, 1927-1930 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Kwan, C. C. - Nanking, China, 1926-1929 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Laboratory Mill - (Correspd. regarding such), 1925 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Lamson, Herbert D. - China, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Love, H. H. - College, 1927-1929 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Lowdermilk, W. C. (see also correspd. in personal files), 1927 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - North, Eric M. - New York City, 1925-1927 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Owen, L. J., 1927 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Relsner, J. H. - China, 1925-1930 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Rose, Wickliffe - New York City; Tsunghan Hunt Shen, 1895-1980 (Ph.D. '28), 1926-1927 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Shen, T. H. - Nanking, China (see also grad student folder; also, p. 29, Box 9, Folder 18; Thesis: The inheritance of earliness and its relation to height of plant in winter wheat crosses. SB/124/1928/S546), 1925-1930 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Travel Correspondence ' financial arrangements, itineraries, etc., 1925-1930 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Wang Sheo - Nanking, China, 1927-1930 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Eake, T. - France, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Plant Industry, Bureau of, Wash., B. C., 1925-1927 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Porter, R. H. - China, 1925-1927 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Reports from Myers and Wiggans, 1926-1928 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Ritchey, G. E. - China, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Pih, R. V. - Kaifeng, China, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Foreign Student Committee, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Foreign Student Committee, Jan.-July 1938 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Foreign Student Committee, Aug.-Sept. 1938 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Foreign Student Committee, Oct. -Dec. 1938 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Foreign Student Committee, Jan. -Mar., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Foreign Student Committee, Apr. 1939-1947 & n. d. (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Chinese Student Aid - Applications, n. d. (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Chinese Student Aid, 1937-May 1938 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Chinese Student Aid, June 1938-Oct. 1938 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Chinese Student Aid, Nov. 1938-Mar. 1939 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Chinese Student Aid, Apr. 1939-1941 & n. d. (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, 1940-1944 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, n. d. (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Miscellaneous, 1937-1938, & n. d. (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - 2 Newspapers, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - 2 Newspapers, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- First Presbyterian Church ' Minutes of Committee Meetings, Sessions, etc. 1935-1938. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Minutes of Committee Meetings, Sessions, etc. 1940-1941. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Minutes of Committee Meetings, Sessions, etc. 1942-1943. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Minutes of Committee Meetings, Sessions, etc. 1944-1946. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Minutes of Committee Meetings, Sessions, etc. 1947. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Minutes of Committee Meetings, Sessions, etc. 1948. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Minutes of Committee Meetings, Sessions, etc. 1949-1950. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Minutes of Committee Meetings, Sessions, etc. N. D. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- First Presbyterian Church Budget 1936-1942. (Box 5, Folder 9)
- First Presbyterian Church Budget 1936-1942. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- First Presbyterian Church Budget 1943-1946. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- First Presbyterian Church Budget 1948-1949. (Box 5, Folder 12)
- First Presbyterian Church Budget 1949-1950. (Box 5, Folder 13)
- First Presbyterian Church ' Rules and Regulations N. D. (Box 5, Folder 14)
- First Presbyterian Church ' Rules and Regulations N. D. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Nominating Committee of 1948. (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Candidates for the Pastorate 1936. (Box 5, Folder 17)
- First Presbyterian Church Sunday School ' A Report 1936. (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Questionnaires and Answers N. D. (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Questionnaires and Answers N. D. (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Martin D. Hardin 1936-1938. Memorial address; note from widow, Julia (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Programs of other Churches 1931-1936. (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Programs of other Churches 1937-1939. (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Programs of Other Churches 1940-1941. (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Programs of Other Churches 1942-1949 + N. D. (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Correspondence from Thailand, China, etc. Manuscript ' re: Puerto Rican Experimental Station 1940. (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Part I - The Measure of Variability pp. 1-28. (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Part II - Analysis of Variance pp. 29-69. (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Part III - Analysis of Correlation and Covariance pp. 70-116. (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Part IV - Practical Application of the Analysis of Variance to Field Experiments Sec. 1 and 2 pp. 117-130. (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Part IV - Practical Application of the Analysis of Variance to Field Experiments Sec. 3 and 4 pp. 130-155. (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Part IV - Practical Application of the Analysis of Variance to Field Experiments Sec. 5 and 6 pp. 156-197. (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Part IV - Practical Application of the Analysis of Variance to Field Experiments Sec. 7-9 pp. 198-223. (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Part V - General Suggestions for the Conduct of Experiments Sec. 1-5 pp. 224-289. (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Fart V - General Suggestions for the Conduct of Experiments Sec. 6-10 pp. 290-235. (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Appendix (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Manuscript. Wong, A Winter Barley for New York, 24 pages N. D. (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous Information on Wong Barley 1942-1946. (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Pictures of Barley, etc. N. D. (Box 5, Folder 39)
- 3 Speeches and Papers by H. H. Love N. D. (Box 5, Folder 40)
- 3 Speeches and Papers by H. H. Love N. D. (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Manuscript. "Investigations in Plot Technic with Small Grains," 1938. (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Reports on Methods N. D. (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Lyon, T. L. ' College 1907-1922. (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Love, H. H. - P. B. 1907-1917. (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Mann, Prof. A. R. - College of Agriculture 1908-1913. (Box 5, Folder 46)
- The Present Status of Agricultural Education Development in Asia and the Far East (Report). - 1960. (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Miscellaneous Letters 1925-1962. (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Pamphlets on Agriculture in the Rural Church - China 1920-1936. (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Pamphlets on Chinese Forestry, Agriculture, Culture, and Education 1925-1926. (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Chinese Experimental Station Reports 1925-1926. (Box 5, Folder 51)
- "The Chinese-Tibetan Borderland and Its Peoples" by Paul Huston Stevenson 1927. (Box 5, Folder 52)
- 2 Pamphlets: On Christianity and War; and Chinese Economics 1928 + N. D. (Box 5, Folder 53)
- 2 Pamphlets on Wheat written in Chinese N. D. (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Agricultural Reprints, Tables, etc. 1911-1950. (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Bessel's and Peter's Formulas, Om's Calculations, Tables of Odds N. D. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Correlation Ratio, Partial Cor. Coefficient, St. Line, Regression, Parabola, Los. Curve, Binomial Expansion N. D. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Yield Factors; Length of Row, Number of Plots 1930-1937. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Statistical Notes N. D. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Determination of Odds, Analysis of Variance 1932 + N. D. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Radio Talks 1934. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Radio Talks 1935. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Radio Talks 1936. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Radio Talks 1937. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Radio Talks 1936. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Radio Talks 1939-1940. (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Radio Talks 1941. (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Radio Talks 1942. (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Radio Talks 1943. (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Radio Talks 1944. (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Radio Talks 1945-1947. (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Radio Talks 1948-1949. (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Radio Talks N. D. (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Report on Daisy Work 1914 + N. D. (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Story of the Yorkwin Wheat 1928. (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Pennsylvania Lecture 1937. (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Lecture Tours 1921. (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Lecture Tours 1922 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Lecture Tours Jan.-Mar. 1923. (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Lecture Tours Apr.-Oct. 1923. (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Lecture Tours Nov.- Dec. 1923. (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Lecture Tours Jan.-May 1924. (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Lecture Tours June-Dec. 1924. (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Lecture Tours 1925 + N. D. (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Germination of Seed as Affected by Sulfuric Acid Treatment Paper No. 24. (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Information and Pictures Relating to Paper No. 24. (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Laboratory of Experimental Plant-Breeding Papers Nos. 17, 29, 31, 52, 59. (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Laboratory of Experimental Plant-Breeding Papers Nos. 63, 64, 67, 68. (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Laboratory of Experimental Plant-Breeding Papers Nos. 70, 75, 76. (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Laboratory of Experimental Plant-Breeding Papers Nos. 102, 103, 114, 118. (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Laboratory of Experimental Plant-Breeding Papers Nos. 119, 129 (including pictures). (Box 6, Folder 37)
- The Inheritance of Velvet Node in a Cross Between Two Varieties of Wheat Paper No. 130. (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Results of Experiments with Oats in New York Paper No. 137. (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Laboratory of Experimental Plant-Breeding Papers Nos. 151, 152, 154 and graphs. (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Laboratory of Experimental Plant-Breeding Papers Nos. 157, 158. (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Two Papers on Experimental Methods N. D. (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Charts, Statistics, and Inheritance N. D. (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Better Wheat for New York 1948. (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Original Manuscripts and Data Inf. on 1913-1917. (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Original Manuscripts and Data N. D. (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Original Manuscripts and Data N. D. (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Original Manuscripts and Data 1917 + N. D. (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Miscellaneous Data (Barley, Rust Resistance, Corn Cockle) 1913-1921. (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Illinois Experiment Station ' Corn Data, etc. 1910. (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Reports ' Department of Commerce and Labor N. D. Bureau of Markets 1917. (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Abstracts and Translations of Articles N. D. (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Earlier Articles by H. H. Love N. D. (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Notes on Germany 1914 + N. D. (Box 6, Folder 54)
- A Speech on the Early Breeding of the Plant-Breeding Department 1961. (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Letters Re: the History of the Plant-Breeding Dept. 1962. (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Material Re: Nanking N. D. (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Articles on Nanking Plant- Breeding N. D. (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Nanking: Plant-Breeding, Training, etc. N. D. (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Plant-Breeding-Protection, International and Government Cooperation N. D. (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Manuscripts later published as Cornell International Agricultural Development Bulletin #4, 1964, 52 pp. Mann Library has; call # HD/82/C814/no. 4. ("... first notable example of international technical cooperation in agriculture... " W. I. Myers)
  - Manuscript ' "The Cornell-Nanking Story" (typed carbon) [1924-1931] Love and Reisner, - also letters re: it, 1963. (Box 6, Folder 6l)
  - Andrews' Letter, plus Mailing Lists of the Story 1964 + N. D. (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - "The Cornell-Nanking Story" (typed and with pictures) plus correspondence 1963-1964. (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Bound Copy of the Manuscript with Corrections N. D. (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Papers re: Manuscript, changes, corrections and correspondence 1963-1964. (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Photographs and Negatives N. D. [Negatives removed to neg. file, 12/2/86] (Box 6, Folder 66)
- 3 Pamphlets re: Plant-Breeding and China, 1932-1934. (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Correspondence-- A. 1917-1949 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Akemine, Prof. M., Japan. 1923-1939 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Includes correspondence concerning the unauthorized use of HHL's tables of statistics by a third party (1938-1939).
- Alter, S. Neale, Syria. 1936-1940 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  SNA, a Presbyterian missionary to Syria, concerning need for technical assistance in agriculture among Bedouin peasants; desirable for missionaries to have this type of training, as well as theological studies. Also, a few letters to Mrs. Love from Mrs. Alter re: their life and work, the effect of the coming of World War II, and other matters.
- American Association for the Advancement of Science 1914-1915 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- American Genetic Association 1932-1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- American Society of Agronomy 1915-1050 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- American Society of Agronomy Symposium Jan. -Sept. 1922 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- American Society of Agronomy Symposium Oct. 1922-1923 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 8)
- American Society of Agronomy, New Orleans Meeting (Nov. 22-24, 1939) 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- American Society of Naturalists 1912-1946 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Atkinson, Alfred 1914-1946 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Correspondence B 1930-1948 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Ball, Carleton R. 1912-1930 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Beckley, Mrs. A. B. 1934 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Boshnakian, Sarkis 1920-1931 Geologist, Maracaibo, Venezuela. (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Bussell, F. P. 1921-1949 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Correspondence C 1942-1949 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Canadian Society of Technical Agriculturists 1924 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Capo, E. G. Rio Piedras, P. R. 1940-1950 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Carson, Arthur L. 1926-1945 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching 1928-1943 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Cayuga Heights Village 1926-1931. Width of sts.; school tuition. (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Cereal Finances N. D. (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Committee- Affiliation Between N. Y. S. College of Agr. and Geneva Experiment Station 1906-1919 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Committee-Experiment Station Organization 1909-1928 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Committee - Experiment Station Organization N. D. (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Committee - Coordination Resident Research, and Extension Teaching 1924 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Committee - Graduate School (General) 1934 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Committee - Grain Standardization 1924 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Committee Nominations 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Committee - Projects 1919 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Committee - Publications 1915-1916 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Committee Publications 1917 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Committee Publications N. D. (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Committee Social Science Research 1947 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Committee - Standardization of Field Experiments 1921-1924 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Committee - Standardization of Field Experiments 1925-1930 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Committee - Varietal Nomenclature and 1920-1926 Standardization (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Committee - Varietal Registration-Oats 1926-1929 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Craig, W. T. 1910-1942 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Correspondence -D- 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Davenport, Eugene Urbana, Illinois 1919-1936 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Day, President E. E. Cornell University 1937 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Dorsey, M. J. 1909-1941 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- East, E. M. 1909-1915 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Emerson, R. A. 1920-1942 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Evans, Mrs. Laura B. 1915-1931 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Expense Accounts N. D. (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Faculty 1918-1933 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Faculty 1934-1939 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Faculty 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Faculty 1945 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Faculty 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Faculty 1949 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Faria, Dr. Carlos V. Areia, Brasil 1939-1941. Advice on statistic methods. (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Farrand, Livingston 1927-1937. Tuition for Love children, etc. (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Feehan, F. 1931-1933 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Foreign Economic Administration- 1943-Oct. 1944 Geo. M. Reynolds-M. N. Knapp (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Foreign Economic Administration- Nov. 1944 - Mar. 1945 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Foreign Economic Administration- Apr. - Dec. 1945 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Fraser, A. C. 1918-1936 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Correspondence -G- 1929-1950 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Gillis, M. Q. Champaign, Illinois 1935-1944 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Guiscafre-Arrillaga, Dr. J., Mayaguea, P. R. 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Guterman, Dr. C. E. F. College 1939-1944 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Correspondence -H- 1949 (Box 7, Folder 66)